Morton Gould Papers
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music, 1920-1995 (Box 1-104, 146)
  - Stage Works, 1945-1983
    - Fall river legend (ballet), 1948, Scores, sketches; Laid in: list of movements, list of movements for Foster gallery, track listing; Commissioned by Ballet Theatre (Box-folder 28/3-4, 84/4)
    - Interplay (ballet), 1945, Score; Other title: American concertette (Box-folder 28/5-6)
    - Rib of Eve (ballet), 1956, Scores; Based on Gould's Dance variations; For Ballet Theatre (Box-folder 29/1)
    - Something to do (musical), 1976, Scores, sketches; Laid in: program, correspondence, program note, scripts; Commissioned by the U.S. Department of Labor for presentation on Labor Day 1976 (Box-folder 29/2-5, 30/1, 84/5)
    - Tread the green grass: a folk fantasy in 3 acts, undated, Score; Incomplete (Box-folder 103/5)
    - World of tomorrow (World's Fair theme song), 1962, Score (Box-folder 30/2)
  - Film and Television, 1940-1994
    - Celebration ’81 (telecast), 1981, Scores, sketches; For NBC telecast, "Live from Studio 8H" (Box-folder 30/3)
    - Cinerama holiday (film), 1955; transcribed for strings, trumpet, percussion, and optional percussion, 1994, Scores, sketches (Box-folder 30/4-5, 84/6)
    - F. Scott Fitzgerald in Hollywood (television), 1976, Score, sketches; Laid in: orchestral booking sheet, cue sheet, correspondence, synopsis (Box-folder 31/1, 85/1)
    - The four of us (television pilot), 1976, Sketches; Laid in: orchestral booking sheet, cue sheet, ephemera (Box-folder 31/2)
    - Holocaust (television), 1978, Scores, sketches (Box-folder 85/2)
    - Land of hope (television), 1976, Score, sketches (Box-folder 31/3, 85/3)
    - Ring of steel (film), 1942, Score (Box-folder 31/4)
    - San Francisco conference (film), 1940, Score, sketches; For the Office of War Information (Box-folder 31/5)
    - The secret of freedom (television), 1960, Sketches (Box-folder 31/6)
    - The turn of the century (television), 1960, Score (Box-folder 31/7, 85/5)
    - Windjammer (film), 1958, Scores, sketches; Laid in: timing sheet (Box-folder 32/1-2, 86/1)
    - World War I (television), 1964-1965, Scores, drafts, sketches; Laid in: cue sheets, program lineup, correspondence; Scores, sketches, and cue sheets arranged by episode (Box-folder 32/3-4, 33-35, 86/2-5, 87-88, 95/1-2)
  - Chamber and Solo Instrumental, 1920-1995
    - 2nd march and Waltz (piano), 1930, Score (Box-folder 103/6)
    - American caprice (piano), 1940, Score (Box-folder 36/1)
    - Anniversary rag (piano), 1994, Scores; For WNYC's 50th anniversary; Other title: WNYC FM rag (Box-folder 36/2)
    - BDG 70 (clarinet, double bass), 1979, Score; Laid in: correspondence; For Benny Goodman's 70th birthday (Box-folder 36/3)
    - Benny's gig: 8 duos (clarinet, double bass), 1962, Score, sketches; In celebration of Benny Goodman's 1962 Russian tour (Box-folder 36/4)
    - A birthday trifle for an untrifling occasion: Aaron at 80 (piano), 1980, Score, sketches; Laid in: program note; For Aaron Copland's 80th birthday celebration at Symphony Space, "Wall-to-wall Copland" (Box-folder 36/5)
    - Boogie the woogie (piano), undated, Sketches (Box-folder 36/6)
    - Boogie the woogie etude (piano), 1943, Score (Box-folder 36/7)
    - Bouquet for [Jack] Benny (trumpets, trombones, violin), 1970, Score (Box-folder 36/8)
    - ‘Cellos (violoncellos), 1984, Score, parts, sketches; Laid in: corrections sheet, programs; For Mstislav Rostropovich and the Second American Cello Congress; Commissioned by the Arizona State University Centennial Commission (Box-folder 36/9-10, 89/1)
    - Challenge (tap dancer, percussion), 1956, Score, part, sketches; Laid in: correspondence (Box-folder 36/11)
    - Concerto concertante (violin, wind quintet, piano), 1982, Scores, parts, sketches; Laid in: program note, programs; Commissioned by the McKim Fund in the Library of Congress (Box-folder 36/12, 37/1-2)
    - Dance gallery (piano), 1950?, Score (Box-folder 37/3)
    - Dance novelties (piano), circa 1931, Scores; Titles: Dance novelty; Dancing marionette; Pygmy; Tin general (Box-folder 103/7)
    - Du-o for tu-o (You know who-o) (flute, clarinet), 1972, Score (Box-folder 37/4)
    - Flutefare (flute), 1986, Score; For WFMT Chicago anniversary (Box-folder 37/5)
    - Ghost waltzes (piano), 1991, Scores, sketches; Laid in: correspondence; Commissioned by Louis F. Kornfeld for the 9th Van Cliburn International Piano Competition (Box-folder 37/6)
    - Harvest (strings, harp, vibraphone), 1945, Score (Box-folder 103/8)
    - Just six: Waltz Viennese (piano), 1920, Score (Box-folder 37/7)
    - Lullaby for a new born love (piano), 1938, Score (Box-folder 37/8)
    - Maazel tov music (violin), 1986, Score; For Loren and Dietlinde Maazel (Box-folder 37/9)
    - Marionette in motley (piano), 1932, Score (Box-folder 37/10)
    - M.G. to M.G. (solo percussion), 1966, Score, sketches; Laid in: correspondence; To Moe Goldenberg (Box-folder 37/11)
    - New China (piano), undated, Score (Box-folder 37/12)
    - Parade (percussion), 1956, Score (Box-folder 37/13)
    - Patterns (piano), 1984, Scores, sketches; Laid in: correspondence; Commissioned by the U.S. Information Agency for its Artistic Ambassador Program (Box-folder 37/14)
    - Percussion piece, undated, Score (Box-folder 37/15)
    - Pieces of China (piano), 1985, Score, sketches; Laid in: timing sheet, ephemera; For Jacques d’Amboise (Box-folder 37/16)
    - Pop's serenade (piano), 1945, Score; For Paul "Pops" Whiteman (Box-folder 38/1)
    - Popular dances for piano, undated, Sketches (Box-folder 38/2)
    - Prelude and toccata (piano), 1944, Sketches (Box-folder 38/3)
    - Prologue (piano), 1945, Sketches (Box-folder 38/4)
    - Rag waltz (piano), 1984, Score; For Edward Villella (Box-folder 38/5)
    - Rags and blues (piano), 1955?, Sketches (Box-folder 38/6)
    - Recovery music for Benny Goodman (clarinet), 1984, Score (Box-folder 38/7)
    - Sonata no. 3 (piano), 1936, Sketch (Box-folder 38/8)
    - Song and dance for alto sax, 1995, Score; For President Bill Clinton (Box-folder 38/9)
    - String quintet op. 1, no. 238 1/3 (string quartet, bassoon), undated, Score, parts; Laid in: program notes (Box-folder 38/10)
    - Suite for cello and piano, 1981, Score, parts, sketches; Laid in: programs, ephemera; Commissioned by the Chamber Music Society of Lincoln Center for Leslie Parnas and Charles Wadsworth (Box-folder 38/11, 89/2)
    - Suite for tuba (tuba, horns), 1971, Score, sketches; For Bill Bell (Box-folder 38/12)
    - Suite for violin and piano, 1945, Score, parts; Laid in: correspondence (Box-folder 38/13)
    - Tango (piano), undated, Scores; Multiple versions (Box-folder 103/9)
    - Theme, variations, and fugue in Romantic style (piano), 1931, Score, sketches (Box-folder 39/1)
    - Tropical (piano), 1938, Score (Box-folder 39/2)
    - Two pianos, 1987, Score, sketches; Laid in: correspondence, program; Commissioned by the Murray Dranoff Foundation for the first national two-piano competition (Box-folder 39/3)
    - Valse modernique (piano), circa 1930s, Score (Box-folder 103/10)
    - Waltz passacaglia and toccata (piano), 1952, Sketches (Box-folder 39/4)
  - Vocal, 1941-1995
    - 2 Herrick songs (voice, piano), 1932, Score (Box-folder 103/11)
    - 4 pop songs (voice, piano), 1936, Scores; No lyrics (Box-folder 103/12)
    - 5 songs (voice, piano), 1965, Score; Titles: Egg shell world; Most reluctantly; The money; Temple bell; Somewhere (Box-folder 103/13)
    - A capella for double chorus, 1987, Score; Commissioned by a consortium of choruses: Chanticleer, The Gregg Smith Singers, Plymouth Music Series, Oratorio Society of Washington (Box-folder 39/5)
    - The banjo (chorus), undated, Parts (Box-folder 39/6)
    - Birthday songs (voice, piano), undated, Scores; 16 titles (Box-folder 39/7)
    - Calypso serenade: Island of sunshine, undated, Lead sheet (Box-folder 39/8)
    - Dancing days, 1965, Lead sheet (Box-folder 39/9)
    - A growing place (voice, piano), 1973, Scores, sketches (Box-folder 39/10)
    - Hamaariv arovim (tenor solo, mixed chorus, organ), 1947, Score (Box-folder 39/11)
    - Happy to you (voice, piano), undated, Score; Other title: Shirley's song (Box-folder 39/12)
    - Just another name for John (voice, piano), undated, Sketches (Box-folder 39/13)
    - No longer very clear (voice, piano), 1994, Scores, sketches; Laid in: correspondence; Commissioned by WNYC FM for its 50th anniversary (Box-folder 39/14)
    - Of time and the river (chorus), 1946, Scores, sketches; Laid in: programs, correspondence (Box-folder 40/1-2)
    - Picnic in the park (voice, piano), Score (Box-folder 40/3)
    - Quotations (double chorus, wind ensemble), 1983, Scores, sketches; Laid in: program; Commissioned by L. Anthony Fisher for the New York Choral Society (Box-folder 40/4, 89/3, 95/3)
    - Serenade of carols (double chorus, 2 pianos), undated, Score (Box-folder 40/5)
    - Sir Walter Winchell: the noble night owl (voice, piano), undated, Score; Vocal line only; Sketch of "There ought to be a law" on verso (Box-folder 103/14)
    - Some songs for September (voice, piano), 1987, Score; Wedding music (Box-folder 40/6)
    - A song for freedom (narrator, chorus, orchestra), 1941, Score (Box-folder 89/4)
    - There are no children here (children’s chorus), 1995, Scores, sketches; Laid in: program, correspondence; For the New York Young People's Chorus (Box-folder 89/5)
    - Two for chorus (voices, piano, percussion), 1966, Scores (Box-folder 40/7)
    - Watch America (voice, piano), Score (Box-folder 40/8)
    - Work (voices, piano, clarinet, percussion), undated, Score (Box-folder 103/15)
  - Miscellaneous Sketches, 1931-1995
    - 1958 May-1966 October, Sketch books (Box-folder 41/1-8)
    - 1967 April-1971 October, Sketch books (Box-folder 42/1-6)
    - 1971 June-1972 July, Sketch books (Box-folder 43/1-4)
    - 1972 July-1974 Winter, Sketch books (Box-folder 44/1-4)
    - 1974 February-1975 December, Sketch books (Box-folder 45/1-5)
    - 1976 December-1980 August, Sketch books (Box-folder 46/1-6)
    - 1980 August-1981 December, Sketch books (Box-folder 47/1-6)
    - 1982 January-1987 May, Sketch books (Box-folder 48/1-5)
    - 1986 Summer-1995, Sketch books, leaves (Box-folder 49/1-6)
    - Ballet music: lullaby (Box-folder 50/1)
    - Ballet rejects (Box-folder 50/2)
    - Christopher Columbus: concerto for bassoon (Box-folder 50/3)
    - Concerto for piano and chamber ensemble, undated, Score (Box-folder 103/16)
    - Crinoline and lace (Box-folder 50/4)
    - DADE -- Harmonica rag or no. 4 (Box-folder 50/5)
    - Fanfares (Box-folder 50/6)
    - Four piano sketches (Box-folder 50/7)
    - Heritage (Box-folder 50/8)
    - Johnny Appleseed ballet, 1957, Laid in: plot sketch (Box-folder 50/9)
    - Johnny Appleseed ballet II, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 50/10)
    - Latin album (Box-folder 50/11)
    - Miscellany, 1953-1993, undated (Box-folder 51-54/5, 104/1-6)
    - Rumbolero, 1931 (Box-folder 104/7)
    - The scene (Box-folder 54/6)
    - Study in fourths (Box-folder 104/8)
    - Symphony (Box-folder 104/9)
    - Symphony no. 1, No relation to Gould's Symphony no. 1, 1942 (Box-folder 104/10)
    - 'Tis of thee (Box-folder 54/7)
    - Tropical storm (Box-folder 54/8)
    - Turkey in the straw -- Reuben, Reuben, I've been thinking (Box-folder 54/9)
    - TV themes, used and unused, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 54/10)
    - An untitled musical comedy, Based on a play by John Patrick, M. Gould, Timothy Gray, and Danny Daniels; Laid in: rough outline, production notes (Box-folder 54/11)
    - Vintage of '76 (Box-folder 54/12)
    - Weill sketches (Box-folder 54/13)
    - Why (Box-folder 54/14)
  - Arrangements
    Undated works for orchestra unless otherwise indicated.
    - 4 Afro-Cuban dances, Score (Box-folder 89/6)
    - Adeste fideles: O come, all ye faithful (band), Score (Box-folder 55/1)
    - Address unknown, Score, parts (Box-folder 96/1)
    - Adios, Score (Box-folder 89/7)
    - All God's children (strings), 1961, Score (Box-folder 55/2)
    - Almost like being in love (strings, harp, celeste), Score (Box-folder 55/4)
    - American patrol (3 marching bands), Score (Box-folder 55/3)
    - Amor, 1964, Scores (Box-folder 55/5)
    - Andalucia suite, Score (Box-folder 89/9)
    - Anna, Score (Box-folder 90/1)
    - Anything goes, Score, parts (Box-folder 55/6)
    - Anything goes medley, Score, parts (Box-folder 55/7)
    - Arthur Schwartz medley (chorus, orchestra), Score, parts (Box-folder 55/8)
    - At home abroad medley, Score, parts; Laid in: sheet music used for arrangement (Box-folder 55/9)
    - Ay-ay-ay, Score (Box-folder 55/10)
    - The bambuco, Parts (Box-folder 56/1)
    - Battle hymn (band), Scores (Box-folder 56/2)
    - Beginners luck, Score, parts (Box-folder 56/3)
    - Berlin medley, Score, parts (Box-folder 56/4)
    - Bernard and Mann, Score, parts (Box-folder 90/2)
    - Bewitched, Score; Laid in: sheet music used for arrangement (Box-folder 56/5)
    - Beyond the sea, Score, sketch (Box-folder 56/6)
    - Big broadcast of 1936, Parts (Box-folder 56/7)
    - The bilbao song, Score (Box-folder 56/8)
    - Birthday (strings), Parts (Box-folder 56/9)
    - Brazil, Score (Box-folder 56/10)
    - Broadway melody of 1936, Score, parts (Box-folder 57/1)
    - Broadway melody of 1936, Score, parts (Box-folder 57/2)
    - Camptown races, Score, parts (Box-folder 57/3)
    - Carry me back to Old Virginny (strings), Parts (Box-folder 57/4)
    - Chorale and fugue on the Volga boatman (2 pianos), Score (Box-folder 104/11)
    - The continental, Score (Box-folder 57/5)
    - Dark eyes, Scores, parts (Box-folder 57/6)
    - Deep river (strings), Score, tenor saxophone part (Box-folder 58/1)
    - Desafinado, Scores (Box-folder 90/3)
    - Does your heart beat for me, Score, parts (Box-folder 96/2)
    - Doing the prom, Score, parts (Box-folder 58/2)
    - Don't look now (Box-folder 96/3)
    - Don't worry about me, Score, parts (Box-folder 96/4)
    - East side of Heaven, Score, parts (Box-folder 96/5)
    - Easy to love, Score (Box-folder 58/3)
    - En tres por quatro, Scores (Box-folder 90/4)
    - Encantado, Score (Box-folder 90/5)
    - Espana cani, Score (Box-folder 58/4)
    - Ezekiel saw the wheel (strings), 1961, Score (Box-folder 58/5)
    - A fine romance, Score, parts (Box-folder 58/6)
    - The first noel (band), Score, sketch? (Box-folder 58/7)
    - Flederhaus waltz (2 pianos), 1935, Score (Box-folder 104/12)
    - Flying down to Rio, Score, parts (Box-folder 58/8)
    - Follow the fleet medley (voice, orchestra), Score, parts; Laid in: sheet music used for arrangement (Box-folder 58/9)
    - The gentleman awaits, Score, parts (Box-folder 59/1)
    - The girlfriend (wind quintet), Score, parts (Box-folder 59/2)
    - Good King Wenceslas, Scores (Box-folder 59/3)
    - Good morning, Score, parts (Box-folder 97/1)
    - Goodnight sweetheart, Score (Box-folder 59/4)
    - Gospel train (strings, harp), 1961, Score; Other title: Old time religion (Box-folder 59/5)
    - Grande valse brilliante (Chopin, op. 18), Score (Box-folder 90/6)
    - Green fields and bluebirds, Score, parts (Box-folder 59/6)
    - Gregg Smith Christmas concert (chorus, orchestra), Scores, parts; Laid in: letter from Gregg Smith (Box-folder 59/7)
    - Here's to romance (voice, orchestra), Score, parts; Laid in: sheet music used for arrangement (Box-folder 59/8)
    - Hit the deck, Score, parts (Box-folder 59/9)
    - The hills of old Wyoming, Score, parts (Box-folder 59/9)
    - The Hoiriger Schottische, Score (Box-folder 97/2)
    - Home for Christmas, Orchestration list only (Box-folder 60/1)
    - How can I ever be alone?, Score, parts (Box-folder 97/3)
    - How can we be wrong, Score, parts (Box-folder 97/4)
    - How high the moon, Score, parts (Box-folder 97/5)
    - A-hunting I will go, Score, parts (Box-folder 60/2)
    - I can't get started (piano, orchestra), Score (Box-folder 60/3)
    - I can't give you anything but love, Score, parts (Box-folder 60/4)
    - I got a marble and a star, Score (Box-folder 60/5)
    - I got rhythm, Scores; Two different arrangements (Box-folder 90/7)
    - I haven't time to be a millionaire, Score, parts (Box-folder 98/1)
    - I love thee, Score (Box-folder 60/6)
    - I love to whistle, Score, parts (Box-folder 98/2)
    - I love you, Score (Box-folder 60/7)
    - I nearly let love go slipping through my fingers, Score, parts; Laid in: sheet music used for arrangement (Box-folder 60/8)
    - I wish I were Aladdin (voice, orchestra), Score, parts (Box-folder 60/9)
    - I'll follow my secret heart (string orchestra, harp, percussion), Score (Box-folder 60/10)
    - I'm in the mood for love, Score (Box-folder 60/11)
    - In a monastery garden (voice, chorus, orchestra), Score, parts (Box-folder 60/12)
    - In the still of the night, Parts (Box-folder 60/13)
    - Island in the West Indies, 1936, Score, parts (Box-folder 60/14)
    - It came upon the midnight clear (winds), Score, 1 part (Box-folder 61/1)
    - It might as well be Spring (piano, orchestra), Score, sketch; Laid in: sheet music used for arrangement (Box-folder 61/2)
    - It's delightful to be married, Scores, parts (Box-folder 90/8)
    - I’ve got no strings, Score, parts (Box-folder 98/3)
    - J’attends un navire (string orchestra), Score (Box-folder 61/3)
    - Jamaica farewell, Score (Box-folder 90/9)
    - Jay walk, Scores, parts; Two different arrangements (Box-folder 61/4)
    - Jingle bells, Score (Box-folder 61/5)
    - Kamennoi ostrow, Score (Box-folder 98/4)
    - King of Burlesque, 2 parts only (Box-folder 61/6)
    - Let's fall in love (string orchestra), Scores (Box-folder 61/7)
    - Let's put our heads together, Score, parts (Box-folder 61/8)
    - Let's put out the lights, Score (Box-folder 61/9)
    - Liebesträume (Liszt), Score (Box-folder 98/5)
    - Little David (Play on your harp) (harp, string orchestra), 1961, Score (Box-folder 61/10)
    - O little town of Bethlehem and Away in a manger (winds, horns), Score (Box-folder 61/11)
    - Liza, Score, parts (Box-folder 99/1)
    - The lonely little music box, Score, parts (Box-folder 99/2)
    - Lost in meditation, 1938, Score, parts (Box-folder 99/3)
    - Lost in the stars, Score (Box-folder 91/1)
    - Love never went to college, Score, parts (Box-folder 99/4)
    - Love is a powerful thing, Score, parts (Box-folder 61/12)
    - Love song of Tahiti, Score, parts (Box-folder 61/13)
    - Love walked in, Score (Box-folder 91/2)
    - A lovers lullaby, Score, parts (Box-folder 100/1)
    - Mac the Knife: Berlin, Scores (Box-folder 61/14)
    - Mac the Knife: New York, Score (Box-folder 61/15)
    - Mad about the boy, Score, parts; Laid in: sheet music used for arrangement (Box-folder 62/1)
    - Mahoganny. Theme, Score (Box-folder 91/3)
    - Make believe (piano, orchestra), Score, sketch (Box-folder 62/2)
    - Male quartet arrangements, Scores, parts (Box-folder 62/3)
    - Mama Inez, Score, parts (Box-folder 62/4)
    - Manhattan holiday, Score, parts (Box-folder 62/5)
    - March militaire (Schubert, op 51, no. 1), Score (Box-folder 100/2)
    - Medley insertion: Darling Nellie Gray; Oh Susannah; Arkansas traveler, Score, parts (Box-folder 100/3)
    - The merry farmer (Schumann, op. 68, no. 10) (winds, horns), Score (Box-folder 63/1)
    - Midnight in Paris, Score, parts; Laid in: sheet music used for arrangement (Box-folder 63/2)
    - Minute waltz (Chopin) (band, harps), Score (Box-folder 91/4)
    - Miss Hallelujah Brown, Score, parts (Box-folder 100/4)
    - Moment musical (Schubert) (band, harps), Score (Box-folder 100/5)
    - The moon is in tears tonight, Score, parts; Laid in: sheet music used for arrangement (Box-folder 63/3)
    - Moonlight and roses (men's voices, orchestra), Score, parts (Box-folder 63/4)
    - Moonlight in Hilo, Score, parts; Laid in: sheet music used for arrangement (Box-folder 63/5)
    - More: theme from Mondo Cane, Score (Box-folder 91/5)
    - More than you know, Parts; Laid in: sheet music used for arrangement (Box-folder 63/6)
    - My blue heaven, Score, parts (Box-folder 63/7)
    - My romance, Parts; Laid in: sheet music used for arrangement (Box-folder 63/8)
    - My rosary of broken dreams, Score, parts (Box-folder 101/1)
    - My ship, Scores (Box-folder 63/9)
    - My silent love, Score (Box-folder 63/10)
    - My silent love (voice, orchestra), Score, parts (Box-folder 63/11)
    - Never on Sunday (mandolin, orchestra), Score (Box-folder 91/6)
    - The night is young and you're beautiful, Score, parts; Laid in: sheet music used for arrangement (Box-folder 63/12)
    - No greater love, Score (Box-folder 64/1)
    - On your toes, Score, parts (Box-folder 64/2)
    - One note samba, Score (Box-folder 91/7)
    - Oriental nocturne, Score, parts; Laid in: sheet music used for arrangement (Box-folder 64/3)
    - The peanut vendor, Scores, parts (Box-folder 64/4)
    - The penguin, Score, parts; Laid in: sheet music used for arrangement (Box-folder 64/5)
    - Play fiddle play, Score, parts (Box-folder 64/6)
    - Polly's lied (strings, winds), Score; Laid in: sheet music used for arrangement (Box-folder 64/7)
    - Porgy and Bess suite, Scores (Box-folder 64/8)
    - Prelude in C sharp minor (Rachmaninoff, op. 3, no. 2), Score (Box-folder 101/2)
    - Preview: The prima donna; Dancing in the dark, Score, parts (Box-folder 64/9)
    - Redheads on parade medley (voice, orchestra), Score, parts (Box-folder 65/1)
    - Reverie (Debussy), Score (Box-folder 104/13)
    - The revolt of the yes men, Score, parts (Box-folder 65/2)
    - September song, Score (Box-folder 65/3)
    - Shine, Score, parts (Box-folder 91/8)
    - Siboney, Score (Box-folder 91/9)
    - Serenade for a wealthy widow, Score, parts (Box-folder 65/4)
    - Silent night (band), Score (Box-folder 65/5)
    - Soft lights and sweet music, Score (Box-folder 65/6)
    - La soirée dans grenade (Debussy), Score (Box-folder 104/14)
    - Somebody nobody knows, Parts (Box-folder 65/7)
    - Sometimes I feel like a motherless child (strings), 1941, Scores, parts (Box-folder 65/8)
    - La sorella, Score, parts (Box-folder 91/10)
    - Speak low (harp, strings), Score (Box-folder 66/2)
    - Speak to me of love (harp, strings), Score (Box-folder 66/3)
    - Spirituals (string orchestra), Scores; 4 titles (Box-folder 66/4)
    - Spring song (Mendelssohn, op. 62, no. 6), Score (Box-folder 66/5)
    - Stars and stripes forever (3 pianos, orchestra), 1953, Score; For Steinway and Sons centennial celebration (Box-folder 91/11)
    - Stompin’ at the Savoy, Score, parts (Box-folder 66/6)
    - Stop look and listen (Box-folder 66/7)
    - Surabaya Johnny, Score (Box-folder 91/12)
    - Swanee River in the style of ..., Score; 11 titles for various composers (Box-folder 91/13)
    - Sweet and lovely, Score, parts (Box-folder 66/8)
    - Sweet surrender medley, Score, parts (Box-folder 66/9)
    - Tea for two, Score (Box-folder 67/1)
    - Tell me that you love me, Score, parts (Box-folder 67/2)
    - These foolish things (Remind me of you), Score, parts (Box-folder 67/3)
    - Through your eyes to your heart, Score (Box-folder 67/4)
    - Tiger rag, Score, parts (Box-folder 67/5)
    - Time on my hands, Score, parts (Box-folder 67/6)
    - The tinkle song, Score, parts (Box-folder 101/3)
    - Tomorrow is another day (voice, orchestra), Score, parts; Laid in: sheet music used for arrangement (Box-folder 67/7)
    - Train to Johannesburg, Score (Box-folder 67/8)
    - Traumerei (Schumann, op. 15, no. 7) (harp, strings), Score (Box-folder 91/14)
    - Unforgettable (voice, orchestra), Score, parts (Box-folder 67/9)
    - Vagabond kind medley (chorus, orchestra), Score, parts, sketches (Box-folder 68/1)
    - Vamos (Let's not talk), Score (Box-folder 91/15)
    - La vent dans la plaine (Debussy), Score (Box-folder 104/15)